icicilombard.com 2012-10-17

# Privacy Policy of ICICI Lombard

We value you as a customer and respect your right to privacy. In the process of operating the Web Site, we may become aware of information relating to you, including information that is of a confidential nature. We are strongly committed to protecting your privacy online and have taken steps to protect such information. To aid us in protecting your privacy, you should maintain secrecy of your login ID and password, if any, provided to you in connection with your account with www.icicilombard.com 

**Collecting your personal information**

ICICI Lombard may collect the information you provide when you: | •| Request information from ICICI Lombard's Web site.   
---|---  
• | Use online tools and calculators.   
---|---  
• | Apply online for products.   
---|---  
• | Subscribe to online services.   
---|---  
• | Complete an online form.   
---|---  
• | Conduct transactions online.   
---|---  
• | Apply for a job online.   
---|---  
  
We collect contact information such as your name, address, and email address and other details as given in the registration page of our website. If you purchase a policy from us we will collect financial information such as credit card number and expiration date through the payment gateway of the credit card company or the Internet banking service of your bank. We store this information for our records and in order to verify authenticity of the same. We also collect information such as beneficiary name, address and your relationship to the beneficiary when you buy a policy from us. This is required to maintain a record of your beneficiary details for your insurance with us.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friends name and e-mail address. Your friend will automatically be sent a one-time e-mail inviting him or her to visit the website.

**Use of your personal information**

We will use the information primarily for the following purposes:  • | By using this website you authorize us to contact you via email or phone on your contact details provided above and offer you information and services for the product you have opted for. You authorize us to call you for the mentioned purpose for a period of upto 30 days irrespective of whether you are registered with the NDNC registry.  
---|---  
• | Allow you to access specific account information.  
• | Providing customization: We may use the information provided by you to customize your visit to the Web Site by displaying appropriate content at our judgment and discretion.  
---|---  
• | To send you information about products and services offered by ICICI Lombard and its Affiliates, to contact you for policy reminder notices, claims processing and to keep you updated on the insurance sector and ICICI Lombard through our newsletters. In event you do not wish to receive such information, you may unsubscribe through the facility in the email message you receive.   
---|---  
• | To contact you for policy reminder notices, claims processing and to keep you updated on the insurance sector and ICICI Lombard through our newsletters.   
---|---  
  
**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to help us customize your visit to our website so that you like the experience. However, we would like to reiterate that this information is not shared with third parties, for their promotional purposes, except as provided under **Disclosure of Information** clause.

**Use of Cookies**

We store a cookie on your computer when you visit our Web site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a users computer for record-keeping purposes. The primary purpose of these cookies is to analyze how users move within our Web site. Our cookies let you view customized pages while transacting with us. Our cookies do not have confidential or personally identifiable information. Since, we use session ID cookies, they do not track a user after leaving our Web site. A session ID cookie expires when you close the browser. It is required if you want to buy a policy online from us. We also use analytic tools to track visitor traffic on website. 

Some of our business partners such as chat support use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.icicilombard.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties. 

**Disclosure of Information**

Subject to the other terms contained herein, we will not disclose your information to any third parties or affiliates for their promotional purposes, unless acting under a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: • | Conform to any statutory or legal requirements or comply with legal process or judicial orders  
---|---  
• | Protect, enforce and defend our rights or property  
---|---  
• | Protect our interests or interests of ICICI Bank Group Companies.   
---|---  
  
We may also use your personal information for the purposes of providing you with any services and service-related activities. In this regard, it may be necessary to disclose your personal information to one or more service providers (eg. Third Party Administrators for Cashless Hospitalisation, National Do Not Call Registry for filtering before Call related activities) of ICICI Lombard providing services linked to Insurance sector to fulfill your requests. 

We reserve the right to exchange, share or provide the information relating to your personal and financial details and information with other ICICI Bank Group Companies or Statutory Bodies as required and you will not hold us and/or any other group companies of ICICI Bank Group and their agents liable for use or sharing of the information. 

We obtain your permission to post testimonials which may include your personal information prior to posting on this website. If you would like your testimonial removed, please contact us at: [insuranceonline@icicilombard.com](mailto:insuranceonline@icicilombard.com)

We use service providers to fulfill some of the service requests on this site including live chat, third party administrators for cashless claims and health checkup and motor surveyors for vehicle inspection. We do not share, or sell your personal information to third parties. These service providers are not allowed to use your information for their promotional purposes.

**Updating your personal information**

If you need to update your personal information or there is any change in the personal information, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or delete it by making the change on our registration page or by emailing our Website team at [insuranceonline@icicilombard.com](mailto:insuranceonline@icicilombard.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as credit card number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://wp.netscape.com/eng/ssl3/>

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we do not guarantee its absolute security. 

**Links to other sites**

The Web Site may contain links to other sites and/or portals on the Internet. While we intend to link only to such sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by such other sites. 

Please be aware that websites that have links from our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. This privacy statement does not cover the information and disclosure practices of those web sites. When you leave our site, please read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time by posting the same on the Website, so please review it frequently on the Website. If we materially change our privacy practices we will notify you by sending an email or by posting a notice on our web site.

 **Business transitions**  
In the event ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via [email] [prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days] of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 

The Website team  
ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company,   
401-402, Interface Bldg; No.11,   
Link Road, Malad (West),   
Mumbai - 400064.   
Tel No. +91 22 3983 9999.  
Email: [insuranceonline@icicilombard.com](mailto:insuranceonline@icicilombard.com)
